LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
So, they haven't found this place yet.
Well, I guess I'll wait until it's night time.
Gunpowder Smoke
and a
Hail of Bullets
I'm honoured that you remembered the Ministry of Justice.
In any case, this must be quite a predicament for you.
You have my sympathies.
I don't have much time,
so I'll be direct.
While Section 9 has been officially dismantled, my subordinates are still evading capture.
I wish to protect their personal safety; not Section 9's good name.
Can you persuade the Committee with this?
Even if I could, it would be impossible to placate the Prime Minister.
That is, not until the Lower House elections quiet down.
For now, protect Yakushima; after the elections, oust the Secretary General,
give the media a scandal,
and the people the illusion of social justice;
that would be the approximation of the Prime Minister's scenario.
In exchange for my subordinates lives?
As long as you survive, the organisation can be rebuilt.
There is no need for you to commit double suicide with Section 9.
If I miss the current opportunity,
I will never again be able to assemble such an exceptional team.
I cannot reconstruct Section 9 without them.
Please stop the car.
Yakushima's influence is great.
I am sure that building a case against Yakushima is a long-cherished goal for the prosecutors,
but in the end, the prosecutors only exist because of the State.
What are you going to do?
Would you like to take this back with you?
No. I will leave it with you.
Then why aren't you bowing and begging?
Doing so is only effective if one is in a superior position.
Am I wrong?
No, you are quite right.
Please don't take this personally.
I wish I could hear more news about Section 9...
The war is getting worse.
What?
Yeah. So that's how things are, Gramps.
The war is getting worse. You know the building that exploded yesterday?
I was living there before I came here.
This place is pretty comfortable, and I like you guys, too,
but there is someone I want to help, no matter what.
The war is getting worse.
Gramps, this is...!
Thanks, Gramps!
I'm going!
Deciphering read code.
Sixteen minutes until packeting of information is complete and dissemination can commence.
Good.
Quiet.
Follow our orders and exit the building.
Colonel, we have completed the evacuation of civilians from the building.
Good.
Begin confiscating evidence.
Roger.
Good.
Sorry about that, guys.
What happened?!
Give me a status report, now!
Just a little payback.
You think you can keep us here without letting us evacuate?
You must be Ishikawa.
As soon as casualties are recovered,
reorganize the team with the remaining members.
We will withdraw from the premises.
We won't find anything in there.
How unfortunate...
You will pay for my subordinates deaths.
I'll make you pray for death before the end.
Colonel, the net at the safe house has caught some prey.
Is it the female leader?
No, it is the male gorilla with cybernetic eyes.
Dispatch the reinforced exoskeleton units that were left on duty.
Roger.
Batou-kun... you kept the natural oil!
Yo!
Wait, why are you here?
On Tachikoma's
Eye: Matsukei Construction
Arm: Safety First
A rebel should act like one until the end!
I guess it means that we all share the same desires, despite our divergence.
We all have the same desire to save Batou-San!
Besides... that explosive shell you're holding...
You can't load that by yourself, can you?
Nope...
But are we the only ones here?
I'm the only one who survived out of the group that was sent to the labs.
I was left to rot after I was connected to some equipment for a final experiment,
so I tore out the cord and ran away!
I myself was unable to stay put where I was, a high-altitude construction site.
And you?
My story's about the same.
What happened to the lab group?
Oh yeah, they were all dismantled.
Remember the one who was always reading books?
He got his brain picked apart the second we reached the labs.
He seemed to actually be happy about that, though.
I see...
I guess everyone got to experience death, then.
I knew you'd do it, Major.
You're not one to skimp on the details.
Don't do it!
Put the gun down!
Okay.
I surrender.
Bingo.
I thought she'd be the type to hide them around here.
He's finally down.
Damn, I killed him.
I see.
Do I look dead to you?
Sorry. I stole your eyes.
Jesus Christ...
There's more of them?
You caused unnecessary casualties...
To hell with taking him alive!
I'll take you back as a corpse!
But before that...
This is for the team members you killed!
And that one was for my partner you killed!
What the...?
Get Batou-San to safety!
Roger!
Sentient tanks!
I'm going first!
Batou-San, sorry for being late.
We got held up trying to eavesdrop on the enemy's com systems.
I'll get him and come back, so please wait here.
Dammit...
Where were they hiding?
Do you think you can immobilize him somehow, with the wires?
I'll try!
What are they trying to do?
I see...
Why, you...!
I must be patient.
I only have one shot.
Now!
Fire!
Okay!
Take this!
Why?!
So it was a dud...
I'm still alive?
Oh, God...
How...
powerless we are...
That isn't necessarily true.
What you have attained is anything but powerlessness.
That voice is...
This is my last!
Now!
O-Okay!
Batou-San...!
Goodbye, Batou-San...
The second unit's response signal also disappeared.
It's hard to believe, but were they both destroyed?
I will make that decision.
For now, all you have to do is get us to the site.
Why did these two...?
They escaped from the labs because they wanted to save you.
Major!
I had made up my mind that they were useless as weapons, since their AIs had evolved too far.
However, as they proactively gathered information and repeatedly underwent synchronisation,
they acquired individuality and the will to sacrifice.
If only I had realised it sooner...
I could have confirmed whether or not they had gained ghosts.
Ghost...
If they weren't here,
you'd be dead by now.
Let's get out of here.
You can see Section 9 really well from here.
To think that you'd have a safe house here, of all places...
Hey!
It doesn't feel right unless I'm in this body.
It was being remotely controlled, eh?
That's right.
Oh, yeah.
I was about to miss getting this to you.
Just as I thought.
No matter how many times you switch bodies,
that watch has been keeping your elapsed lifetime for each one.
The flow of time that passes us by...
It is because people wish to record proof that defines their individuality, their ego,
that they entrust it to external mnemonic devises.
Isn't that thing the only thing that can define who you are - your external mnemonic device?
When did you get so serious?
A watch and bodybuilding...
we both have been clinging to pointless fragments of our memory, haven't we?
We are most likely the only Section 9 members who have not been captured.
Let's keep going and preserve a record of what we were trying to do.
Well, it's not as if I can die in peace without having met my goals.
Primary sniping target : Kusanagi Motoko.
The committee has issued an order for her elimination.
This is our only chance.
Shoot the moment they start boarding.
Motoko!
Motoko!!!
Vital signs: negative.
Destruction of target, confirmed.
Dammit...
Motoko!!!
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up